is fluen boards a better solution to
Trello the answer is no in fact fluen
boards is inspired by Trello designed
specifically for the WordPress Community
bringing you all the features you love
with extra perks with Flo boards you get
unlimited assignes complete control over
your data and Flawless WordPress
compatibility right within your familiar
WordPress dashboard get all at once when
you migrate all your Trello projects
into fluent boards without losing a bit
of it let me show you to begin you'll
need to export your Trello project in
Json format it's a simple process just
open the menu on your Trello board and
select the option to export s Json now
what you have to do is head over to
boards tab in the fluent boards
dashboard click on the more icon and
you'll find the import options choose
the option for Trello upload your Json
file and start the import process it's
as simple as
that your project is now on fluent
boards just like they were in
Trello now that we have our project on
fluent boards let's take a quick look
inside the first thing worth noting is
that you have three views to choose from
list view calendar view and conon view
moving tasks between stages is so smooth
do you see this
this really helps maintain a clear
representation of your task progress if
you need more stages just add them with
a simple double click change the stage
name go ahead create as many tasks as
you need there are no limits you can
even rearrange tasks and stages by
dragging and dropping them into place
amazing isn't it now let me show you
what's inside a task each task in fluent
boards is packed with features to keep
you organized just double click to give
your task a clear and concise title need
to assign team members no problem you'll
see your WordPress users on the list
ready to be assigned you can also set a
due date with a specific time and
prioritize the task urgency this is lit
one of the key parts of your task is the
description this is where you outline
what needs to be done providing all the
essential details thanks to its Rich
Text field you can add bullet points
insert links change alignment and
utilize many other features to keep your
description well organized so handy
right in the task you can also attach
relevant files documents links or images
directly to the task for easy access
it's like having everything you need
under one
umbrella when tasks get complexed
flyboard steps up with Advanced features
to keep things under control you might
ask how well you can easily break the
tasks down into manageable subtasks and
assign users to each one plus the
comment section right here is great for
team communication and the activity log
keeps a clear record of all tweaks and
updates Floy boards also offers custom
Fields tailored to your specific project
needs plus you can create checklists to
make sure every step is completed so
practical let's check out a few more
features from the menu ooh as you can
see you can change the background of
your board it's not just limited to
these few options you can also set one
on your own beat your own choice of
background color or any image
wow now a very important point that I'd
like to mention is keeping your assignes
and clients notified about the current
stage of your project I feel like
personally for me this feature stands
out as I constantly need to stay
notified to stay on track so Flo boards
lets you enable email notification
comment assigned to a task due date
whenever A Change Is made your board
members will be notified since fln
boards is tailor made for WordPress it
features some fantastic Integrations
fluent boards work seamlessly with
fluent forms fluent CRM fluent support
and fluent
SMTP and the best part more Integrations
are on the horizon exciting right last
but not the least reports reports
influent boards gives you a full
overview of your project offering
valuable insights at a glance as you can
see you'll get a clear picture of how
your projects are progressing with very
insights plus the front-end portal
brings you to a clean intuitive
interface for smooth and efficient task
and project management keeping
everything the same without backend
access no privacy concerns right both
Trello and flu boards offers a free
version to get started when you decide
to go premium Trello costs $120 yearly
unlocking the standard plan features
plus some additional ones on the other
hand with fluent boards you get all
features included in any plan you buy so
you'll never feel short on features this
is also an ongoing lifetime deal for
fluent boards costing only $149 for a
single domain plan which includes
lifetime updates and support being
affordable and compatible with WordPress
flu boards is a solution for every task
every team so get flu boards now and
manage your projects with the ultimate
efficiency
[Music]